I joined the Shoulder to Shoulder group about four months ago and during this period I saw
a significant improvement in my business and in my personal life.
I have less stress because I know what to focus on.
I have more time in between where I can really sit down and think about things because every
week what we do is we sit together with an amazing group of like-minded entrepreneurs.
We talk about our bottlenecks and the focus points for this week and we really go in
depth.
We are on a surface level but we also reach a problem behind the problem.
So it's an amazing group of guys so if you're an entrepreneur looking for like-minded people
who can really go in depth on your business then this is definitely for you.